Search

Search

PRIVACY NOTICE
==============

Revised Date: July 11, 2024

Auto Accident Team and its affiliated companies (“we” or “us”) respect the privacy of all individuals. This Privacy Policy (the “Privacy Policy”) governs our collection, use, and disclosure of your Personal Information (as defined below) in connection with your use of our website(s) on which this Privacy Policy is linked (collectively, “Sites”) and any transactions, interactions, or other engagements you might have with us (collectively, “Services”). For clarity, the term “Sites” does not include any sites owned or operated by third parties.

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. By using the Sites or Services, you consent to the collection and use of your information by us as set out in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy forms a part of and is incorporated into our [Terms of Service](https://autoaccidentteam.com/terms-of-use/), and any capitalized terms used but not otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy will have the meanings given to them in the Terms of Service. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, YOU ARE NOT PERMITTED TO USE OR ACCESS THE SITE.

**ABOUT THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

**Privacy Policy Changes**

This Privacy Policy is subject to change. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy frequently for any revisions or amendments. If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, the revised policy will be posted on the Sites with the date of revision. Changes will be effective immediately upon posting. You will be deemed to have been made aware of and have accepted the changes by your continued use of our Sites or Services. If we determine that a change to this Privacy Policy will result in using your Personal Information acquired before the change being used in a materially new way, we will provide notice, such as by a posting on the Sites or an email to your last known email address, before using your Personal Information in the new way.

**Conflict Between this Policy and Laws and Regulations**

When federal, state, or local laws and regulations require a higher level of protection for your Personal Information, they take precedence over this Privacy Policy. The specific requirements of this Privacy Policy apply unless disallowed by applicable laws or regulations. Please be aware that the Sites and Services are subject to the laws of the United States of America and that your Personal Information will be processed in the United States and other jurisdictions. The Sites and Services are intended for use by individuals in the United States.

**INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

**Personal Information**

We may collect information that personally identifies, relates to, describes, or is capable of being associated with you (“Personal Information”), including:

* _Identifiers and Contact Information_ such as name, address, email address, phone number;
* _Personal Identifiers_ such as education, employment status, financial information, and health insurance information;
* _Protected Classification Characteristics_ such as age, marital status, gender, and veteran or military status;
* _Health Information_ such as a medical condition or diagnosis related to your request;
* _Commercial Information_ such as the products that you have used, considered, or purchased;
* _Internet and Network Information_ such as IP address, device ID, browsing/search history, browser type, device type and settings;

The specific Personal Information we collect about you may vary based on how you use the Sites and/or Services and your relationship with us.

**Usage Data and Sites Activity**

We automatically collect information in connection with the actions you take on the Sites (“Usage Data”). For example, each time you visit our Sites, we may automatically collect the type of web browser you use, the type of device you use, the type of your operating system, the name of your Internet Service Provider, the pages you view on our Sites, referring and exit pages, the date and time of your visit, and the number of clicks to, from, and within the Sites, and the duration of your visits to the Sites. If this information is reasonably capable of being associated with you, we treat it as Personal Information under the category Internet and Network Information. If this information is not reasonably capable of being individually associated with you, we treat it as Usage Data.

**Communication Recordings**

We may record calls and retain the content of text messages or other written/electronic communications between you and us. By communicating with us, you explicitly consent to our recording and retention of communications.

**HOW WE COLLECT INFORMATION**

**From You**

We may ask you to provide us with Personal Information when you communicate with us (online or offline), use the Sites or Services, enter into a relationship with us, and at other times. You are not required to provide us your Personal Information; however, if you choose not to provide the requested information, you may not be able to use some or all of the features of the Sites or Services or we may not be able to fulfill your requested interaction.

**Cookies and Other Automated Tools**

We and third parties use cookies (small text files placed on your computer to identify your computer and browser) and other automated tools such as pixels to track your interaction with our Sites and to improve the experience of our Sites and Services, such as saving your preferences from visit to visit to present you with a customized version of the Website. Many web browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, certain features of our Sites may not work if you delete or disable cookies.

We use the following types of cookies:

* _Strictly Necessary:_ These cookies are essential to operate the Sites and provide you with services you have requested.
* _Functional:_ These cookies enable certain features or non-essential functionality on our Sites. For example, we might use these cookies to recognize you and remember your preferences or settings when you return to our Sites so we can provide you with a more personalized experience.
* _Advertising Cookies:_ These cookies allow us and third parties to learn more about you, including your use of our Sites and other websites, and to advertise products or services that might interest you as further indicated below.
* _Analytics Cookies:_ These cookies help us and third parties understand how our Sites are working and who is visiting our Sites.

We and third parties also use tools that enable us to track certain aspects of a user’s visit to our Sites. This technology helps us better manage content on our Sites by informing us what content is effective, how consumers engage with our Sites, and how consumers arrive at and/or depart from our Sites. The software typically uses two methods to track user activity: (1) “tracking pixels” and (2) “clear gifs.” Tracking pixels are pieces of executable code embedded in a web page that track usage activity including which pages are viewed, when they are viewed, and how long the pages are viewed. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with unique identifiers embedded in web pages and email messages that track whether a user views a web page or email message. User activity information may be associated with additional information about a user’s session and Personal Information, if provided by the user.

You can opt-out of certain types of cookies and other tracking tools by clicking the cookie settings icon at the bottom of applicable Sites.

If you arrive at our Sites by “clicking through” from another website, then certain information about you that you provided to that other website, such as the terms you searched that led you to our Sites, may be transmitted to us and we may use it. You should review the Privacy Policy of any website from which you reached our Sites to determine what information the operator collects and how it uses such information. We may retain information about you provided to us by other websites and will use it in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Such information may be associated with other Usage Data or Personal Information.

**Interest-Based Advertising**

We may work with third-party advertisers, search providers, and ad networks (“Ad Networks”) to learn more about you and show you ads or other content that we believe would be relevant to you. Advertisers may collect and use information about your use of our Sites or Services as well as other websites and services. These companies may use cookies and other online tracking technologies to collect and use your information. We and/or Ad Networks may also append other data to the data collected by Ad Networks to create an interest profile of individual users. Our Privacy Policy does not cover any use of information that an Ad Network may collect from you except when the Ad Network acts as our service provider. Advertisements may be shown via our Sites or on third-party websites. If you do not want to receive interest-based advertising, please visit the [Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA) Consumer Choice Page.](https://optout.aboutads.info/?c=2&lang=EN) The DAA website allows you to opt-out of one or more interest-based advertising networks. Opt-outs are device and browser specific; therefore, you must set your opt-out preferences for each device and browser. Deleting browser cookies can remove your opt-out preferences; however, the DAA offers [browser extensions](https://youradchoices.com/) that help preserve the opt-out preferences you set on the DAA’s Consumer Choice Page. Please note that opt-outs only apply to interest-based advertising. You may still receive other types of online advertising.

**Partners and Third Parties**

We contract with publishers and other third parties that operate websites that may collect Personal Information about you (“Partners”). When you visit websites of our Partners, you may be redirected to our Sites. We may gather data directly from Partner websites, or our Partners may post data to our Sites or otherwise transfer data to us. This may occur via display ads, click listings, inquiry forms or telephonic transfers from our Partners. We also may receive data from advertisers, advertising agencies, and other parties that our Sites and Services may direct you to in furtherance of your inquiries and requests for goods and services.

**HOW WE USE AND SHARE INFORMATION**

We generally use Personal Information to connect you with advertisers that can provide you with information about the goods and services that you have expressed interest about. We may also use your Personal information for internal purposes, including

* _Providing the Sites and Services;_
* _Marketing and market research:_ such as to send communications and offers and place advertisements, perform analytics for market research, trend analysis, and financial analysis;
* _Other company communications:_ such as to provide you with information that may be of interest;
* _Business operations:_ such as to evaluate, develop, and improve business operations, products and services offered, and perform business administration and other normal business activities;
* _Compliance:_ such as to comply with applicable legal requirements, government requests, industry standards, contractual obligations, our policies, and take actions that we deem necessary to preserve and enforce our rights or the rights of others; and
* _Information security and fraud prevention:_ such as to operate information security and anti-fraud programs.

**Service Providers**

We may establish a relationship with other businesses to provide services to us which may include corporate affiliates (“Service Providers”), including for:

* Provision of the Sites and Services;
* Facilitating marketing, non-marketing, and internal communications;
* Business analytics (both marketing and non-marketing related);
* Project management and collaboration;
* IT and network administration such as data storage and management, website hosting, data security, mobile application development; and
* Day-to-day business operations such as courier services, facilities management, electronic signatures, and document destruction.

We only provide our Service Providers with the Personal Information reasonably necessary for them to perform these services on our behalf. You may also be asked to provide Personal Information directly to a Service Provider. Each Service Provider is expected to use reasonable security measures appropriate to the nature of the information involved to protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. Service Providers are prohibited from using Personal Information other than as specified or permitted by us.

We may share any of the types of Personal Information collected with one or more Service Providers.

**Third-Party Sharing/Selling**

Our providing information to our advertisers, as described above, may constitute “selling” of Personal Information under certain laws, including the California Consumer Protection Act. We share or sell the following types of Personal Information with one or more advertisers: unique identifiers, personal identifiers; protected classification characteristics; health information; commercial information; Internet and Network Information.

**CHILDREN’S PRIVACY**

We do not knowingly collect or solicit Personal Information from anyone under the age of 16. In the event that we learn that we have collected Personal Information from an individual under the age of 16, we will delete that information upon discovery.

**ADDITIONAL STATE LAW CONSUMER RIGHTS**

If you are a resident of California, Colorado, Connecticut, Utah, or Virginia, you have additional rights to access and control your Personal Information. Exemptions may apply.

**Right to Know**

You have the right to request twice per 12-month period that we provide you (i) the categories or specific pieces of Personal Information we collected about you; (ii) the categories of sources from which we collected your Personal Information; (iii) the business or commercial purpose for which we collected your Personal Information; and (iv) the categories of third Parties with whom we shared or sold your Personal Information. We are not permitted to provide access to specific pieces of Personal Information if the Personal Information is sensitive or creates a high risk of potential harm from disclosure to an unauthorized person. To protect consumers’ Personal Information, you must provide required information and/or documentation to verify your identity. We will process verified requests within 45 days, subject to any applicable exceptions and extensions permitted by law.

**Right to Deletion**

You have the right to request that we delete any Personal Information we collected about you. Please understand that we are not required to honor a deletion request if a legal exemption applies such as if we need the information to complete a requested or reasonably anticipated transaction, prevent security incidents or fraud, enable internal uses that are reasonably aligned with your expectations, or comply with legal obligations. We will process verified requests within 45 days, subject to any applicable exceptions and extensions permitted by law.

To prevent unauthorized individuals from making deletion requests, you must provide required information and/or documentation to verify your identity.

**Right to Opt-Out from the Sale of Personal Information**

You have the right to direct us not to sell your Personal Information to third parties. We will process requests within 15 business days, subject to any applicable exceptions and extensions permitted by law.

**Submitting a Request**

If you are a resident of a state that provides privacy rights and you would like to exercise your rights, you may submit a request by email to [info@autoaccidentteam.com](mailto:info@autoaccidentteam.com) or using this [online form](https://autoaccidentteam.com/do-not-sell-my-information/). After you submit your request, we may contact you to obtain additional information necessary to verify your identity. For example, we may require you to verify certain information in our files or submit a signed declaration under penalty of perjury verifying your identity. We will not be able to process certain requests without verifying your identity, so please respond promptly to our request.

**Authorized Agent**

If you are an authorized agent submitting a request on behalf of a California resident, you must provide a copy of a lawful power of attorney or a written signed authorization from the consumer along with proof your identity. You may provide this documentation via email to [info@autoaccidentteam.com](mailto:info@autoaccidentteam.com) after submitting the request. We may contact you and the consumer on whose behalf you claim to act to verify your identity, the consumer’s identity, and your authorization to act on the consumer’s behalf.

**Non-Discrimination Notice**

We will not discriminate against any consumer for exercising their privacy rights under law or this Privacy Policy.

**DO NOT TRACK SIGNALS**

Because there is not yet a consensus on how companies should respond to web browser-based or other “Do Not Track” mechanisms, we currently do not respond to web browser Do Not Track signals that provide a method to opt out of the collection of information about online activities over time and across third party websites or online services. We may revisit our policy on responding to these signals, in which case we will post a revised Privacy Policy on the Sites.

**DATA RETENTION**

We retain your Personal Information for as long as we have a relationship with you. We also retain your Personal Information for a period of time after our relationship with you has ended where there is an ongoing business need to retain it. This includes but is not limited to retention to comply with our legal, regulatory, tax, and/or accounting obligations.

**OTHER TRANSFERS**

We may share Personal Information and Usage Data with businesses controlling, controlled by, or under common control with us. If we are merged, acquired, or sold, or in the event of a transfer of any of our assets, we may disclose or transfer Personal Information and Usage Data in connection therewith.

**COMPLIANCE WITH LAWS AND LAW ENFORCEMENT**

We cooperate with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We may disclose Personal Information, Usage Data, and any other information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties if, in our sole discretion, we believe it is necessary or appropriate to respond to legal requests (including court orders, investigative demands, and subpoenas), to protect the safety, property, or rights of ourselves, consumers, or any other third party, to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical, or legally actionable activity, or to comply with law.

**SECURITY OF YOUR INFORMATION**

We use administrative, technical, and physical security measures to help protect your Personal Information. While we have taken reasonable steps to secure the Personal Information you provide to us, please be aware that despite our efforts no security measures are perfect or impenetrable and no method of data transmission can be guaranteed against any interception or other type of misuse. Any information disclosed online is vulnerable to interception and misuse by unauthorized parties. Therefore, we cannot guarantee complete security if you provide Personal Information to us, and we encourage you to exercise discretion regarding the Personal Information you choose to disclose.

**HOW TO CONTACT US**

If you have any questions about our Sites, Services, or this Privacy Policy, please contact us using the information below.

Auto Accident Team  
Attn: Privacy  
12 Main St.  
Unit #2001  
Brewster, NY 10509  

Copyright © 2024 Auto Accident Team | All rights reserved.

Auto Accident Team is not a law firm nor a lawyer referral service, and it is not providing legal advice. We are a free service that compiles information for individuals seeking legal relief for auto accidents. Auto Accident Team does not endorse or recommend the law firms that participate in our network.

Advertising paid for by participating attorneys in a joint advertising program, including Kevin Danesh, licensed to practice law only in California. A complete list of joint advertising attorneys can be found at [https://www.autoaccidentteam.com/sponsors/](https://autoaccidentteam.com/sponsors/). You can request an attorney by name. 1-800-THE-LAW2 is not a law firm or an attorney referral service. This advertisement is not legal advice and is not a guarantee or prediction of the outcome of your legal matter. Every case is different. The outcome depends on the laws, facts, and circumstances unique to each case. Hiring an attorney is an important decision that should not be based solely on advertising. Request free information about your attorney’s background and experience. This advertising does not imply a higher quality of legal services than that provided by other attorneys. This advertising does not imply that the attorneys are certified specialists or experts in any area of law. No legal services will be provided unless there is a signed agreement between client and attorney.

Search

Search
